<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oddly Specific</title>
    <link>https://jashu.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Oddly Specific</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jashu.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>When 0.1 &#43; 0.2 Does Not Equal 0.3</title>
      <link>https://jashu.github.io/post/comparing_decimal_values/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jashu.github.io/post/comparing_decimal_values/</guid>
      <description>One of the workshops I occasionally give in the IMHR is a review of basic computer-programming principles. I’d say the programming experience for the majority of our psychology students is acquired in a pretty haphazard, piecemeal fashion—usually by learning whatever R they need to know to make it through their statistics coursework and complete their research projects.1 So they invariably end up missing some critical “bits” (pardon the pun) of knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Everything You Know about the P-Value is Wrong</title>
      <link>https://jashu.github.io/post/pvalues1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jashu.github.io/post/pvalues1/</guid>
      <description>I know, yet another post tut-tutting the misuse of p-values. But there are still a lot of folks who are not woke to the problem. Last year, a good friend who is an investigational pharamcist asked for my help in putting together a session on the topic for the 2018 Hospital Pharamcy Practice Seminar, which resulted in an invitation to write a guest article for the fantastic tl;dr pharmacy blog. So, if you want to read my version of the p-value sermon, check out this link to their website:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://jashu.github.io/search/placeholder/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jashu.github.io/search/placeholder/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://jashu.github.io/top/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jashu.github.io/top/about/</guid>
      <description>About this Blog Welcome to my GitHub pages! Here you will find links to R coding tips, tutorials, and in-depth walk-throughs of the data science I am using in my current research collaborations. I hope this will be useful to others in at least two respects:
 For those interested in reproducing research that has been published, you will find the exact code that I used in my data analysis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>